let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "_____ can be defined as a set of activities directed at an organization's resources, with the aim of achieving organizational goals in an efficient and effective manner.",
        answer: "Management",
        options: [
            "Economics", "A theory", "Management", "Self-dealing", "Divestment"]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of the following statements best reflects contemporary management trends?",
        answer: "More and more organizations are using quality as a basis for competition.",
        options: [
            "More and more organizations are using quality as a basis for competition.", "The service sector of the economy has steadily declined.", "Younger people entering the workforce over the past 20 to 30 years are more devoted to work and more willing to adapt.", "The emphasis on business ethics has declined.", "The emphasis on management of diversity has declined."]
    }, {
        numb: 3,
        question: "_____ make decisions about activities such as investing in research and development (R&D) and entering or abandoning various markets.",
        answer: "Top managers",
        options: [
            "Division heads", "Limited partners", "First-line managers", "Middle managers", "Top managers"]
    }, {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following statements about top managers is true?",
        answer: "They officially represent their organization to the external environment.",
        options: [
            "They are the largest group of managers in most organizations.", "They officially represent their organization to the external environment.", "They primarily oversee the day-to-day operations of an organization.", "They supervise and coordinate the activities of first-line managers.", "They supervise and coordinate the activities of operating employees."]
    }, {
        numb: 5,
        question: "_____ is the degree to which the overall task of the organization is broken down and divided into smaller component parts.",
        answer: "Job specialization",
        options: [
            "Job specialization", "Job enrichment", "Job rotation", "Job enlargement", "Task identity"]
    }, {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Creating different teams for finance, production, and marketing is consistent with _____ departmentalization.",
        answer: "Functional",
        options: [
            "Location", "Product", "Functional", "Sequential", "Customer"]
    }, {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What reason do researchers give for their findings that there are more communication problems in tall organizations than flat organizations?",
        answer: "The increased number of people through whom information must pass",
        options: [
            "The smaller number of managers as compared to line workers", "The fewer number of subordinates reporting to each manager", "The increased number of people through whom information must pass", "Reductions in morale tend to prevent employees from communicating effectively", "Reductions in production discourage employees from sharing information"]
    }, {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Ron, a manager at a hardware component manufacturing unit, has recently learned from a subordinate's report that the production rates in his firm have gone down immensely because of poor employee morale. Ron has realized that he needs to make a change in the organization that will motivate employees. Which of the following steps in the comprehensive approach to change is illustrated in the scenario?",
        answer: "Recognizing the need for change",
        options: [
            "Recognizing the need for change", "Understanding how to implement the change", "Setting goals for the change", "Selecting a change technique"]
    }, {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which stage of the Lewin model of organization change involves managers letting people who will be affected by an impending change know the reasons for the change?",
        answer: "Unfreezing",
        options: [
            "Implementing", "Recognizing", "Refreezing", "Transforming", "Unfreezing"]
    }, {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Inflation, the cost of living, and money supplies are all external forces for change in the _____ dimension.",
        answer: "Economic",
        options: [
            "Social", "Political", "Cultural", "Economic", "Technological"]
    }, {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Beta LLC has decided to change its hiring criteria so that more people with technical expertise can join the company. Which step of the change process is illustrated in the scenario?",
        answer: "Selection of appropriate change technique",
        options: [
            "Establishment of goals for the change", "Recognition of the need for change", "Selection of appropriate change technique", "Diagnosis of the relevant variables"]
    }, {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Substantive modification to some part of an organization is known as organization",
        answer: "change.",
        options: [
            "synergy.", "maturity.", "implementation.", "change."]
    }, {
        numb: 13,
        question: "_____ is the financial remuneration given by an organization to its employees in exchange for their work.",
        answer: "Compensation",
        options: [
            "Progression", "Compensation", "An intangible benefit", "Insurance"]
    }, {
        numb: 14,
        question: "A(n) _____ is usually computerized and contains information on each employee's education, work experience, and career aspirations.",
        answer: "skills inventory",
        options: [
            "bona fide occupational qualification", "skills inventory", "statement of qualification", "job description"]
    }, {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Ken is a newly hired police officer. He has been asked to spend a workday with a more experienced officer to learn about paperwork, how to handle accident scenes, how to interact with people, and other duties that he will be expected to perform. Which of the following concepts is illustrated in the scenario?",
        answer: "On-the-job training",
        options: [
            "Performance appraisal", "The assessment center method", "Training manuals", "On-the-job training", "The lecture method"]
    }, {
        numb: 16,
        question: "In human resource management, _____ usually refers to teaching operational or technical employees how to do the job for which they were hired.",
        answer: "Training",
        options: [
            "job rotation", "Development", "Training", "Deskilling"]
    }, {
        numb: 17,
        question: "The _____ lists the duties of a job, the job's working conditions, and the tools, materials, and equipment used to perform it.",
        answer: "job description",
        options: [
            "job specification", "job description", "replacement chart", "statement of qualification"]
    }, {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Windmere allows its administrative employees to arrive any time between 7:00 a.m. and 9:00 a.m., and to leave any time between 4:00 p.m. and 6:00 p.m., as long as they work an eight-hour day. This arrangement is known as",
        answer: "flextime.",
        options: [
            "empowerment.", "compressed work schedule.", "a nine-eighty schedule.", "flextime.", "traditional schedule."]
    }, {
        numb: 19,
        question: "In the two-factor theory, the factors that influence the satisfaction continuum, which are related specifically to work content, are called _____ factors.",
        answer: "Motivation",
        options: [
            "Esteem", "Security", "Environmental", "Motivation"]
    }, {
        numb: 20,
        question: "_____ is the process of giving employees a voice in making decisions about their own work.",
        answer: "Participation",
        options: [
            "Participation", "Empowerment", "Commitment", "Reinforcement"]
    }, {
        numb: 21,
        question: "Brenda, a senior engineer at Machineworks Inc., sets herself difficult goals and assumes personal responsibility for the performance of her subordinates. Brenda most likely has a high need for",
        answer: "achievement.",
        options: [
            "achievement.", "affiliation.", "esteem.", "security"]
    }, {
        numb: 22,
        question: "_____ leader behavior, identified by the path-goal theory, primarily involves being friendly and approachable, showing concern for subordinate welfare, and treating members as equals.",
        answer: "Supportive",
        options: [
            "Directive", "Achievement-oriented", "Task-oriented", "Supportive"]
    }, {
        numb: 23,
        question: "Daniel has been appointed leader of a project task force. He has legitimate power in this position. The task is unstructured. Also, Daniel has weak leader-member relations. According to Fiedler's LPC theory, what type of leadership style is appropriate in this situation?",
        answer: "Task-oriented",
        options: [
            "Task-oriented", "Relationship-oriented", "Participative", "Transformational leadership"]
    }, {
        numb: 24,
        question: "Demonstrating personal excitement or passion about something is part of _____ leadership.",
        answer: "Charismatic",
        options: [
            "Charismatic", "Entrepreneurial", "Symbolic", "Integrative", "Participative"]
    }, {
        numb: 25,
        question: "Punishment involves the use of _____ power.",
        answer: "Coercive",
        options: [
            "Legitimate", "Reward", "Referent", "Coercive"]
    }, {
        numb: 26,
        question: "Recently identified keys to successful leadership such as trusting one's subordinates, developing a vision, and simplifying things are consistent with the premises underlying _____ leadership.",
        answer: "Transformational",
        options: [
            "Contingency", "Transformational", "Charismatic", "Directed", "Situational"]
    }, {
        numb: 27,
        question: "Performance appraisals are part of _____ control.",
        answer: "Human",
        options: [
            "Physical", "Human", "Information", "Financial", "Inventory"]
    }, {
        numb: 28,
        question: "In organizations, sales forecasting, economic forecasting, and environmental analysis are examples of the control of _____ resources.",
        answer: "Information",
        options: [
            "Physical", "Human", "Information", "Financial", "Inventory"]
    }, {
        numb: 29,
        question: "_____ layouts are used in operations settings that create or process a variety of products.",
        answer: "Process",
        options: [
            "Product", "Cellular", "Random", "Process"]
    }, {
        numb: 30,
        question: "Which of the following inventory types provides the components needed to make the product?",
        answer: "Raw materials",
        options: [
            "Raw materials", "Work-in-process", "Merchandise", "Finished goods"]
    }, {
        numb: 31,
        question: "_____ involves selecting a course of action from a set of alternatives.",
        answer: "Decision making",
        options: [
            "Divesting", "Controlling", "Leading", "Decision making", "Organizing"]
    }, {
        numb: 32,
        question: "_____ are probably the largest group of managers in most organizations, and are primarily responsible for implementing the policies and plans of an organization.",
        answer: "Middle managers",
        options: [
            "Middle managers", "Top managers", "The members of the board of directors", "First-line managers", "Floor supervisors"]
    }, {
        numb: 33,
        question: "A _____ is a conceptual framework for organizing knowledge and providing a blueprint for action.",
        answer: "Theory",
        options: [
            "Strategy", "Prediction", "Theory", "Doctrine"]
    }, {
        numb: 34,
        question: "Steve works with Beta Pharmaceuticals Inc. He is primarily responsible for overseeing production activities. Tyler is concerned with decisions such as the number of product units that need to be manufactured, the overall functioning of the production plants, and the quality of products. Steve is most likely to be a(n) _____ manager.",
        answer: "operations",
        options: [
            "operations", "marketing", "human resources", "sales"]
    }, {
        numb: 35,
        question: "Competitors, customers, suppliers, strategic partners, and regulators make up the _____ environment of an organization.",
        answer: "Task",
        options: [
            "Task", "Economic", "Technological", "Political-legal", "Competitive"]
    }, {
        numb: 36,
        question: "A group organized by its members to attempt to influence organizations is known as a(n)",
        answer: "interest group.",
        options: [
            "interest group.", "board of directors.", "strategic ally.", "competitor.", "ethics committee."]
    }, {
        numb: 37,
        question: "Myrtle Wines, a chain of wine retailers, has prepared guidelines that clearly specify how employees should interact with suppliers, customers, competitors, and other people associated with their business. These guidelines are documented and distributed at all Myrtle outlets. The guidelines prepared by Myrtle forms its",
        answer: "code of ethics.",
        options: [
            "business plan.", "strategic plan.", "code of ethics.", "licensing agreement."]
    }, {
        numb: 38,
        question: "Where does an organization's culture originate?",
        answer: "With the organization's founder",
        options: [
            "Societal norms and expectations", "Pressure applied through mergers", "With the organization's founder", "esolution of disputes between rival factions", "Government regulation of the specific industry"]
    }, {
        numb: 39,
        question: "When organizations relate to their environments in ways that involve ethical dilemmas and decisions, these situations are said to fall within the context of the organization's _____ responsibility.",
        answer: "Social",
        options: [
            "Legal", "Ethical", "Social", "Cultural"]
    }, {
        numb: 40,
        question: "What type of plan focuses primarily on people and action?",
        answer: "Tactical",
        options: [
            "Tactical", "Strategic", "Diversified", "Corporate-level", "Business-level"]
    }, {
        numb: 41,
        question: "An organization's _____ is a statement of its fundamental, unique purpose that sets a business apart from other firms of its type and identifies the scope of the business's operations in product and market terms.",
        answer: "Mission",
        options: [
            "Mission", "Statement of qualification", "Article of incorporation", "Operational goal", "Tactical plan"]
    }, {
        numb: 42,
        question: "WexAll Industries has seen demand for its RB37 start to slow down. In addition, the number of other companies producing a similar product has started to go down as well, and there have not been any new entrants into this market. The RB37 is most likely in the _____ stage of the product life cycle.",
        answer: "aturity",
        options: [
            "rowth", "ost-prime", "ntroduction", "aturity", "ecline"]
    }, {
        numb: 43,
        question: "Which of the following strategies will help companies succeed during the growth stage of a product cycle?",
        answer: "Focusing on creating product differentiation",
        options: [
            "Focusing on developing new products or services", "Increasing overhead costs", "Sacrificing product quality", "Focusing on creating product differentiation", "Increasing product prices significantly"]
    }, {
        numb: 44,
        question: "A(n) _____ is an internal skill or capability that does not enable a company to choose and implement strategies that support its mission.",
        answer: "Organizational weakness",
        options: [
            "Organizational weakness", "Organizational threat", "Market threat", "Process gain"]
    }, {
        numb: 45,
        question: "In decision making, a condition of _____ exists when a decision maker knows what the alternatives are and what conditions are associated with each alternative.",
        answer: "Certainty",
        options: [
            "Risk", "Uncertainty", "Certainty", "Ambivalence", "Imperfect information"]
    }, {
        numb: 46,
        question: "Delta Corp. introduced a new set of policies, giving its employees more flexibility in work timings. This decision was made in response to complaints from employees about fatigue. Which step of the rational decision-making process is illustrated in the scenario?",
        answer: "Implementing an alternative",
        options: [
            "Defining the situation", "Evaluating the possible alternatives", "Selecting the alternative", "Implementing an alternative", "Evaluating decision effectiveness"]
    }, {
        numb: 47,
        question: "The classical decision model is a prescriptive approach, meaning that it",
        answer: "tells managers how they should make decisions.",
        options: [
            "provides managers with alternatives.", "tells managers how they should make decisions.", "assumes all decisions are made subjectively.", "allows no room for flexibility.", "describes how decisions often are actually made."]
    }, {
        numb: 48,
        question: "By recognizing the _____ aspect of decision making, the administrative model better reflects subjective considerations.",
        answer: "Behavioral",
        options: [
            "Rational", "Groupthink", "Classical", "Behavioral", "Sequential"]
    }, {
        numb: 49,
        question: "The Delphi group technique is a group decision-making technique in which:",
        answer: "the opinions of group member are combined and averaged.",
        options: [
            "the members are involved in extensive discussions with each other.", "the opinions of group member are combined and averaged.", "the daily operational problems of an organization are addressed.", "the members are most likely to indulge in groupthink.", "the members are most likely to be first-line employees belonging to the same department."]
    }, {
        numb: 50,
        question: "_____ is power that has been legitimized by the organization.",
        answer: "Authority",
        options: [
            "Entropy", "Process gain", "Synergy", "Authority"]
    }, {
        numb: 51,
        question: "Relish Inc. is a large corporation in the food industry that manufactures canned foods, confectionery, and baked foods. The organization has a separate department for each of these types of food manufactured. Each department integrates all the activities required to manage its respective line of food. Which of the following types of departmentalization is illustrated in the scenario?",
        answer: "Product",
        options: [
            "Sequential", "Customer", "Product", "Location", "Functional"]
    }, {
        numb: 52,
        question: "In _____ technology, raw materials are transformed to a finished product by a series of machine transformations in such a way that the composition of the materials themselves is changed.",
        answer: "continuous-process",
        options: [
            "roduct-customization", "large-batch", "mass-production", "continuous-process"]
    }, {
        numb: 53,
        question: "A(n) _____ is a management model of organization design based on a legitimate and formal system of authority.",
        answer: "Bureaucracy",
        options: [
            "Adhocracy", "Bureaucracy", "Entropy", "Autocracy"]
    }, {
        numb: 54,
        question: "Alpha Corp. has divided its business into a number of sub units. This organization change is an example of change in the area of",
        answer: "structure and design.",
        options: [
            "people.", "operations.", "structure and design.", "social responsibility."]
    }, {
        numb: 55,
        question: "What are the three steps in the Lewin model?",
        answer: "Unfreezing, implementing, refreezing",
        options: [
            "Recognizing, planning, implementing", "Unfreezing, implementing, refreezing", "Unfreezing, goal setting, refreezing", "Unfreezing, refreezing, evaluating"]
    }, {
        numb: 56,
        question: "Which of the following can help make the reengineering process more effective?",
        answer: "Creating a sense of urgency in the organization",
        options: [
            "Limiting communication", "Creating a sense of urgency in the organization", "Adopting a highly centralized organizational structure", "Refraining from making extensive changes"]
    }, {
        numb: 57,
        question: "A manager expends extra effort because she has been told that she will get a $50,000 bonus if her team meets its quota. She also feels stress because she has been informed that she will be put on probation if she does not get her team to perform above last year's total. Which of the following does this scenario illustrate?",
        answer: "Performance-to-outcome expectancy",
        options: [
            "Equity theory", "Maslow's esteem needs", "Two-factor theory", "Performance-to-outcome expectancy"]
    }, {
        numb: 58,
        question: "In expectancy theory, raises, promotions, stress and resentment are all _____ of an individual's behaviors.",
        answer: "Outcomes",
        options: [
            "Factors", "Motivations", "Reinforcements", "Outcomes"]
    }, {
        numb: 59,
        question: "_____ focuses on how much people want something and how likely they think they are to get it.",
        answer: "Expectancy theory",
        options: [
            "Maslow's hierarchy", "Two-factor theory", "Expectancy theory", "Reinforcement theory"]
    }, {
        numb: 60,
        question: "Tyler is the marketing manager at MarketAds Inc., and Emily is an account manager reporting to him. Tyler instructs Emily to improve public opinion. The goal that Emily was given lacks goal",
        answer: "specificity.",
        options: [
            "specificity.", "acceptance.", "conformity.", "difficulty."]
    }, {
        numb: 61,
        question: "An individual who is motivating and inspiring people to energize them to overcome barriers by satisfying basic human needs is fulfilling what role and activity?",
        answer: "Leadership role in executing plans",
        options: [
            "Management role in developing a human network", "Leadership role in developing a human network", "Management role in executing plans", "Leadership role in executing plans"]
    }, {
        numb: 62,
        question: "According to the Managerial Grid, a manager who exhibits impoverished management",
        answer: "has little concern for people or for work performance.",
        options: [
            "has little concern for people or for work performance.", "is an effective leader with much concern for people.", "has a lot of concern for people and for work performance.", "has a lot of concern for people, but little concern for work performance."]
    }, {
        numb: 63,
        question: "Sam, the CEO of a company, has the power to take decisions related to resource allocations. His power is mainly derived from his position in the company. Which power is best demonstrated in the given scenario?",
        answer: "Legitimate",
        options: [
            "Reward", "Coercive", "Expert", "Legitimate"]
    }, {
        numb: 64,
        question: "As a property, leadership can be best defined as",
        answer: "a set of characteristics found in people who can influence the behavior of others.",
        options: [
            "the practice of empowering employees to participate in organizational decision making.", "a set of belief that supports the practice of interpersonal risk taking in teams.", "the ability to shape employee behavior without using force.", "a set of characteristics found in people who can influence the behavior of others."]
    }, {
        numb: 65,
        question: "The report issued about a major packaging defect showed a culture at an organization that did not listen when small safety issues were raised. Each issue by itself might not have caused the flaw. This example illustrates",
        answer: "the way that control helps organizations respond to changing standards.",
        options: [
            "the need to understand organizational complexity.", "that changing conditions are influenced by innovation.", "the need for control in order to reduce the accumulation of errors.", "the way that control helps organizations respond to changing standards."]
    }, {
        numb: 66,
        question: "A publishing firm will use a(n) _____ budget to forecast and plan the demand for young adult books in Southeast Asia in the coming year.",
        answer: "Operating",
        options: [
            "Labor", "Capital expenditures", "Operating", "Balance sheet"]
    }, {
        numb: 67,
        question: "_____ include robotic work units or workstations, assembly lines, and robotic carts or some other form of computer-controlled transport system to move material as needed from one part of the system to another.",
        answer: "Flexible manufacturing systems",
        options: [
            "Call-center systems", "Flexible manufacturing systems", "Computer-aided design technologies", "Expert systems"]
    }, {
        numb: 68,
        question: "The management at Loft Corp. has introduced new employment policies. The mangers are now tracking and monitoring the implementation of the new policies. Which of the following management functions is illustrated in the scenario?",
        answer: "Controlling",
        options: [
            "Decision making", "Controlling", "Organizing", "Leading", "Planning"]
    }, {
        numb: 69,
        question: "Steve works with Beta Pharmaceuticals Inc. He is primarily responsible for overseeing production activities. Tyler is concerned with decisions such as the number of product units that need to be manufactured, the overall functioning of the production plants, and the quality of products. Steve is most likely to be a(n) _____ manager.",
        answer: "operations",
        options: [
            "operations", "Marketing", "human resources", "sales"]
    }, {
        numb: 70,
        question: "An international _____ is a set of countries that agree to markedly reduce or eliminate trade barriers among member nations.",
        answer: "economic community",
        options: [
            "Commonwealth", "free trade area", "economic community", "customs union"]
    }, {
        numb: 71,
        question: "In international trade, the _____ amount is typically designed to ensure that domestic competitors will be able to maintain a certain market share.",
        answer: "Quota",
        options: [
            "Benefaction", "Royalty", "Tariff", "Quota", "minimum hourly wage"]
    }, {
        numb: 72,
        question: "Which of the following is a part of an organization's external environment?",
        answer: "Inflation",
        options: [
            "Board of directors", "Physical work environment", "Inflation", "Organization's culture", "Employees"]
    }, {
        numb: 73,
        question: "Alpha Inc. is a large shoe manufacturer that caters to a large customer base. In addition to the high volume of shoes it manufactures, the company sells simple-designed sneakers for low prices. Many customers buy Alpha shoes because they are durable and inexpensive. Which of the following strategies is illustrated in the scenario?",
        answer: "Overall cost leadership strategy",
        options: [
            "Overall cost leadership strategy", "Market diversification strategy", "Differentiation strategy", "Divesting strategy", "Market development strategy"]
    }, {
        numb: 74,
        question: "The top managers at Redd Inc. are developing a plan to reduce the production costs of the company. By reducing costs, Redd wants to gain a competitive advantage of cost leadership. The plan being developed in this scenario is a(n) _____ plan.",
        answer: "Strategic",
        options: [
            "Strategic", "Tactical", "Operational", "Contingency", "recovery"]
    }, {
        numb: 75,
        question: "A difference between tactical and strategic plans is that",
        answer: "tactical plans have a more concrete focus.",
        options: [
            "tactical plans have a more concrete focus.", "tactical plans are set for and by the board of directors.", "tactical plans have broader time horizons.", "strategic plans are developed by first-line managers.", "strategic plans deal with the day-to-day operations of an organization."]
    }, {
        numb: 76,
        question: "Samantha is responsible for building the day-to-day work schedules for her subordinates. She assigns specific tasks to her subordinates and designs activities according to the objectives that she receives from her seniors. Samantha works on _____ goals.",
        answer: "Operational",
        options: [
            "Operational", "Organizational", "Strategic", "tactical"]
    }, {
        numb: 77,
        question: "Zing Inc. is a large fashion brand that manufactures clothing and shoes. The top managers of Zing have decided to use the profits from its clothing outlets to invest in the shoes business. This scenario illustrates the _____ component of a strategy.",
        answer: "resource deployment",
        options: [
            "resource deployment", "Scope", "distinctive competence", "process loss", "divestiture"]
    }, {
        numb: 78,
        question: "R&D at Venus Electronics Inc. has created an innovative new device. Management now needs to decide if Venus should launch this device as its next new product. This is an example of a(n) _____ decision.",
        answer: "Nonprogrammed",
        options: [
            "Frequent", "Nonprogrammed", "Structured", "Operational", "Programmed"]
    }, {
        numb: 79,
        question: "One advantage of group decision making is:",
        answer: "more acceptance of the final decision.",
        options: [
            "groupthink.", "saved time.", "more acceptance of the final decision.", "lowered cost of decision making.", "elimination of political forces."]
    }, {
        numb: 80,
        question: "Which of the following statements is true in the context of decision making under a state of risk?",
        answer: "The decision maker uses probability estimates to assess alternatives.",
        options: [
            "The decision maker clearly knows the alternatives.", "The decision maker uses probability estimates to assess alternatives.", "The decision maker is least likely to choose a bad alternative.", "The decision maker has an accurate understanding of payoffs of all the alternatives.", "The decision maker seldom considers his or her past experience while making the decision."]
    }, {
        numb: 81,
        question: "In which step of the rational decision-making model does the decision maker test the feasibility and satisfactoriness of alternatives before choosing one?",
        answer: "Evaluating alternatives",
        options: [
            "Identifying alternatives", "Implementing the chosen alternative", "Defining the situation", "Following up the implementation", "Evaluating alternatives"]
    }, {
        numb: 82,
        question: "Which of the following statements is true about the decision-making process?",
        answer: "It requires that the nature of a particular situation be defined.",
        options: [
            "It exclusively applies to problem situations.", "It requires that the nature of a particular situation be defined.", "It seldom applies to situations that are positive.", "It typically involves only one individual and seldom applies to groups.", "It results in the generation of only one alternative."]
    }, {
        numb: 83,
        question: "Cedar Enterprises is made up of a number of small units. It has virtually no underlying hierarchy. People float from project to project within their unit, and the organizational design centers on the projects. Cedar is an example of what type of organization?",
        answer: "Team",
        options: [
            "Virtual", "Matrix", "Centralized", "Team"]
    }, {
        numb: 84,
        question: "According to the job characteristics approach, increasing the presence of the five dimensions it identifies will lead to all of the following EXCEPT",
        answer: "higher turnover.",
        options: [
            "higher motivation.", "higher turnover.", "higher-quality performance.", "higher satisfaction.", "lower absenteeism."]
    }, {
        numb: 85,
        question: "_____ is defined as a clear and distinct line of authority among the positions in an organization.",
        answer: "Chain of command",
        options: [
            "Chain of command", "Span of management", "Job deskilling", "Flat structure", "Synergy"]
    }, {
        numb: 86,
        question: "Managers can overcome resistance to change by",
        answer: "announcing the change much in advance.",
        options: [
            "not letting employees know about the change.", "letting employees know about the change only after it has been successfully implemented.", "limiting the involvement of employees in the change process.", "minimizing communication during the change process.", "announcing the change much in advance."]
    }, {
        numb: 87,
        question: "The radical redesign of all aspects of an organization in order to achieve major gains in cost reduction, service delivery, or reduction in order-processing time is known as",
        answer: "reengineering.",
        options: [
            "entropy.", "process change.", "innovation.", "reengineering."]
    }, {
        numb: 88,
        question: "An example of a force for change in the task environment of an organization is",
        answer: "pricing strategies of competitors.",
        options: [
            "pricing strategies of competitors.", "employee turnover rates.", "capital availability.", "employee motivation."]
    }, {
        numb: 89,
        question: "According to the Lewin model of organization change process, refreezing involves",
        answer: "reinforcing the change so that it becomes a part of the system.",
        options: [
            "recognizing why the change is necessary.", "informing people about the change.", "the implementation of the change.", "reinforcing the change so that it becomes a part of the system."]
    }, {
        numb: 90,
        question: "A company has set an objective to increase its product sales by 50 percent in the next two years. Identify the step of the organization change process of the company.",
        answer: "Establishment of goals for the change",
        options: [
            "Recognition of the need for change", "Establishment of goals for the change", "Selection of appropriate change technique", "Planning for implementation of the change"]
    }, {
        numb: 91,
        question: "Pat saw an advertisement for a job opening that she thought she might be suited for. She went to the company's website to look at the job description in order to find out the",
        answer: "tools, materials, and equipment she would have to use to perform the job.",
        options: [
            "skills of existing employees.", "tools, materials, and equipment she would have to use to perform the job.", "educational background required of applicants.", "personal profile of a supervisor."]
    }, {
        numb: 92,
        question: "Top managers at Phoenix Inc. are all computer engineers and are highly regarded by other companies. They are frequently approached by executive search firms with information about openings at other companies. The managers are examples of",
        answer: "knowledge workers.",
        options: [
            "temporary workers.", "emergent workers.", "contingent employees.", "knowledge workers."]
    }, {
        numb: 93,
        question: "_____is an ideal method for training employees in group decision making.",
        answer: "Role-playing",
        options: [
            "Vestibule training", "Programmed learning", "Role-playing", "The lecture method"]
    }, {
        numb: 94,
        question: "Employment requirements such as test scores and other qualifications are legally defined as having a(n) _____ on minorities and women when such individuals meet or pass the requirement at a rate less than 80 percent of the rate of majority group members.",
        answer: "adverse impact",
        options: [
            "affirmative action", "adverse impact", "confirmatory action", "divergent impact"]
    }, {
        numb: 95,
        question: "Working a full forty-hour week in fewer than the traditional five days is called",
        answer: "a compressed work schedule.",
        options: [
            "job sharing.", "flextime.", "a nine-eighty schedule.", "a compressed work schedule."]
    }, {
        numb: 96,
        question: "In what common form of executive compensation are senior managers able to buy shares in the company at a predetermined fixed price?",
        answer: "Stock option plan",
        options: [
            "Gainsharing plan", "Stock option plan", "Profit sharing plan", "ESOP"]
    }, {
        numb: 97,
        question: "Martha is given a new office and a new job title as recognition for her accomplishment over her years of service to the organization. She is satisfied with the recognition and respect from her colleagues. This portrays that the organization is addressing her _____ needs.",
        answer: "Esteem",
        options: [
            "Security", "Physiological", "Belongingness", "Self-actualization", "Esteem"]
    }, {
        numb: 98,
        question: "A manager gives her employees a variable bonus every month based on resulting cost savings every time they exceed their sales quota. This type of incentive pay is known as",
        answer: "gainsharing.",
        options: [
            "fixed-rate pay.", "profit sharing.", "gainsharing.", "lump-sum bonus."]
    }, {
        numb: 99,
        question: "Karl is fond of saying, 'Remember, half the doctors you see graduated in the bottom of their class.' Karl is attempting to limit the _____ power of physicians.",
        answer: "Expert",
        options: [
            "Expert", "Legitimate", "Referent", "reward"]
    }, {
        numb: 100,
        question: "What is the basic assumption of situational approaches to leadership?",
        answer: "The appropriate leader style will vary from one set of circumstances to another.",
        options: [
            "Increasing worker job satisfaction through considerate leadership will get the best results.", "Initiating structure for employees so they know exactly what needs to be done will be most effective.", "The appropriate leader style will vary from one set of circumstances to another.", "Effective leaders can be identified by certain traits."]
    }, {
        numb: 101,
        question: "Carolyn, a manager, discusses and reasons with the Board of Directors of her company until they agree to let her try her new strategic plan for a trial period. Carolyn is using _____ in the given situation.",
        answer: "Persuasion",
        options: [
            "an obligation", "Persuasion", "Coercion", "passive aggression"]
    }, {
        numb: 102,
        question: "_____ skills refer to a manager's ability to prioritize work, to work efficiently, and to delegate work appropriately.",
        answer: "Time management",
        options: [
            "Time management", "Technical", "Conceptual", "Interpersonal", "Communication"]
    }, {
        numb: 103,
        question: "Which of the following is a concern of the technological dimension of an organization's general environment?",
        answer: "Tools, methods, and technology",
        options: [
            "Organization's policies and practices", "Inflation, interest rates, and unemployment", "Tools, methods, and technology", "Government regulations"]
    }, {
        numb: 104,
        question: "Which of the following accurately describes the responsibility of a corporate board of directors?",
        answer: "Ensuring the firm is run to best serve the stockholders' interests",
        options: [
            "Exerting considerable influence by using the media to call attention to their positions", "Helping the company get the expertise they lack from other companies", "Ensuring the firm is run to best serve the stockholders' interests", "Gaining legal property rights to the business by buying stock E. Protecting the public from certain business practices or to protect organizations from one another"]
    }, {
        numb: 105,
        question: "Which of the following statements is true about tactical goals?",
        answer: "Their focus is on how to operationalize actions necessary to achieve strategic goals.",
        options: [
            "Their focus is on how to operationalize actions necessary to achieve strategic goals.", "Their focus is on broad and long-term issues such as increasing the profitability of the organization over a period of time.", "They are set for and by top managers.", "They are set for and by the board of directors. e. They are broad and nonspecific."]
    }, {
        numb: 106,
        question: "In the context of SWOT analysis, which of the following would be considered as an organization's strength?",
        answer: "High employee turnover rate",
        options: [
            "Exiting competitors", "High overhead costs", "Favorable government policies d. Motivated employees", "High employee turnover rate"]
    }, {
        numb: 107,
        question: "Zing Inc. is a large fashion brand that manufactures clothing and shoes. The top managers of Zing have decided to use the profits from its clothing outlets to invest in the shoes business. This scenario illustrates the _____ component of a strategy.",
        answer: "resource deployment",
        options: [
            "resource deployment", "Scope", "distinctive competence", "process loss", "divestiture"]
    }, {
        numb: 108,
        question: "A nonprogrammed decision",
        answer: "requires more time and resources than programmed decisions.",
        options: [
            "is relatively more frequent than programmed decisions.", "is highly structured.", "requires more time and resources than programmed decisions.", "is typically regarding daily organizational transactions.", "typically applies to basic operating systems and procedures."]
    }, {
        numb: 109,
        question: "After being laid off from his job, Joe recognized three options he could choose from before he could secure a new job: to spend less, to use savings, or to use credit. He went over every aspect of his budget, and could not find any area where he could make a cut. Therefore, the option to spend less was immediately eliminated because",
        answer: "it was not feasible.",
        options: [
            "it was not satisfactory.", "it had negative consequences.", "it was not feasible.", "it was not bounded in reality.", "it was not rational."]
    }, {
        numb: 110,
        question: "Pete, a manager, embraces the job characteristics approach. Pete thinks that when his employees have more control over how their work is performed, they do better. Which characteristic is Pete emphasizing?",
        answer: "Autonomy",
        options: [
            "Feedback", "task identity", "task significance", "Autonomy", "skill variety"]
    }, {
        numb: 111,
        question: "What is one of the strengths of the bureaucratic model?",
        answer: "Favoritism and bias are minimized.",
        options: [
            "Favoritism and bias are minimized.", "It is easier to change rules when circumstances change.", "Once rules are understood, it is easier to make exceptions.", "There is a higher level of flexibility.", "More attentions is paid to the human and social processes."]
    }, {
        numb: 112,
        question: "Consumer tastes and preferences are _____ forces that influence an organization's product line.",
        answer: "External",
        options: [
            "Technical", "Internal", "Managerial", "External", "Political"]
    }, {
        numb: 113,
        question: "Alba Inc. replaced old equipment with new and advanced production equipment in all its plants. This is an example of a change in the area of",
        answer: "technology and operations.",
        options: [
            "job design.", "people.", "organization culture.", "technology and operations."]
    }, {
        numb: 114,
        question: "An effective individual strategy for managing a diverse workforce is",
        answer: "encouraging interpersonal communication.",
        options: [
            "encouraging interpersonal communication.", "treating everyone the same without regard for their fundamental human differences.", "creating ethnically homogenous work teams.", "using micromanagement techniques."]
    }, {
        numb: 115,
        question: "_____ reflects an organization's investment in attracting, retaining, and motivating an effective workforce.",
        answer: "Human capital",
        options: [
            "Financial capital", "Human capital", "Surplus capital", "Enterprise capital"]
    }, {
        numb: 116,
        question: "_____ compares each employee with a fixed standard rather than comparison with other employees.",
        answer: "Ranking",
        options: [
            "An objective method", "Rating", "Ranking", "Job specialization"]
    }, {
        numb: 117,
        question: "A performance appraisal system in which managers are evaluated by everyone around them—their boss, their peers, and their subordinates is known as",
        answer: "360-degree feedback.",
        options: [
            "employment at will.", "360-degree feedback.", "source monitoring.", "job evaluation."]
    }, {
        numb: 118,
        question: "Which of the following is a Theory Y assumption?",
        answer: "People do not naturally dislike work.",
        options: [
            "Social processes do not influence the performance of workers.", "People are not internally motivated to achieve their goals.", "People do not naturally dislike work.", "People perform better when they are threatened by the manager.", "People prefer to be directed, to avoid responsibility, and to want security."]
    }, {
        numb: 119,
        question: "Which of the following draws from psychology, sociology, anthropology, economics, and medicine?",
        answer: "Organizational behavior",
        options: [
            "Organizational behavior", "Scientific management", "Administrative management", "Systems perspective", "Contingency perspective"]
    }, {
        numb: 120,
        question: "A company would begin to do business in another country only if the trade relationships with that country are relatively well defined and stable. In the context of general environment, which of the following does this point of view reflect?",
        answer: "Political-legal",
        options: [
            "Task", "Economic", "Technological", "Political-legal", "Competitive"]
    }, {
        numb: 121,
        question: "An international _____ is a set of countries that agree to markedly reduce or eliminate trade barriers among member nations.",
        answer: "economic community",
        options: [
            "Commonwealth", "free trade area", "economic community", "customs union"]
    }, {
        numb: 122,
        question: "A difference between tactical and strategic plans is that",
        answer: "tactical plans have a more concrete focus.",
        options: [
            "tactical plans have a more concrete focus.", "tactical plans are set for and by the board of directors.", "tactical plans have broader time horizons.", "strategic plans are developed by first-line managers.", "strategic plans deal with the day-to-day operations of an organization."]
    }, {
        numb: 123,
        question: "Samantha is responsible for building the day-to-day work schedules for her subordinates. She assigns specific tasks to her subordinates and designs activities according to the objectives that she receives from her seniors. Samantha works on _____ goals.",
        answer: "Operational",
        options: [
            "Operational", "Organizational", "Strategic", "tactical"]
    }, {
        numb: 124,
        question: "The more a manager uses coercive power, the more likely he is to encourage",
        answer: "resentment.",
        options: [
            "sympathy.", "good will.", "resentment.", "tolerance."]
    }, {
        numb: 125,
        question: "An appraisal of an organization's accounting and financial procedures conducted by employees of that organization is known as a(n) _____ audit.",
        answer: "Internal",
        options: [
            "Internal", "Debt", "Ratio", "external"]
    }, {
        numb: 126,
        question: "DayCor has a detailed performance appraisal system. Employees must meet minimally acceptable levels of performance and are rewarded based upon their individual performance. DayCor most likely uses _____ control.",
        answer: "Bureaucratic",
        options: [
            "Strategic", "Decentralized", "Bureaucratic", "Organic"]
    }, {
        numb: 127,
        question: "Which of the following is a financial resource that flows into an organization?",
        answer: "Shareholder investments",
        options: [
            "Shareholder investments", "Working capital", "Retained earnings", "Employee salaries"]
    }, {
        numb: 128,
        question: "_____ control attempts to monitor the quality or quantity of resources before they enter an organization.",
        answer: "Preliminary",
        options: [
            "Structural", "Post-action", "Preliminary", "Screening"]
    }, {
        numb: 129,
        question: "A highest-possible-quality strategy will stress on",
        answer: "quality regardless of cost.",
        options: [
            "the lowest possible cost regardless of quality.", "quality regardless of cost.", "low quality at low cost.", "large quantities at low cost."]
    }, {
        numb: 130,
        question: "If the product is a physical good, operations create value and provide _____ utility by combining many dissimilar inputs to make something that is more valuable than the actual cost of the inputs used to create it.",
        answer: "Form",
        options: [
            "Time", "Form", "Place", "service"]
    }, {
        numb: 131,
        question: "What is the source of control for finished goods inventory?",
        answer: "High-level production scheduling systems",
        options: [
            "Shop floor control systems", "High-level production scheduling systems", "Transportation", "Distribution control systems", "Purchasing models and systems"]
    }, {
        numb: 132,
        question: "Which of the following is true of automation?",
        answer: "Automation helps to improve products and services.",
        options: [
            "The development of automation has created jobs across all industries.", "Automated machines make more errors.", "Automation discourages innovation.", "Automation helps to improve products and services.", "Automation was the earliest step in the development of machines and machine-controlling devices."]
    },
]